

Aneta Kozak

In my case, software testing gradually developed from a field of interest into determined actions. I focus on acquiring knowledge, which resulted in getting the ISTQB Certificate. In order to grow as a Software Quality Assurance Specialist / Software tester I want to learn from more experienced colleagues and get to know the processes of producing software in practice.

aneta.kozak92@gmail.com

+48 697 726 720



Krakow, Poland



anetakozak.eu/

WORK EXPERIENCE

Office Administrator Wolszewski sp. z o.o.

09/2017 - Present

The company specializing in the construction of all sanitary and industrial installations

- Human Resources management, including preparing and conducting training for company's employees, monitoring the validity of occupational medicine examinations, managing employees' work schedule
- Preparing offers, contracts and public tenders as well as negotiating prices and conditions of the deals
- Managing of the financial documents in the internal system
- Filing and archiving documents as well as making sure they are properly cascaded within the company
- Providing office supplies and sanitary facilities for employees on construction sites

NON-COMERCIAL EXPERIENCE

Crowdtesting Project CHERRY-IT (01/2021 - Present)

- Work in SCRAM methodology
- Logging and managing bugs using the Bugtracker tool

Platform uTest.com (10/2020 - Present)

- Performing manual tests of mobile and web application
- Executing test cases
- Creating bug reports
- Writing the summary and rating the product quality

EDUCATION

MSc in IT methods in environmental protection AGH University of Science and Technology in Krakow

03/2015 - 11/2016

BSc in Environmental protection AGH University of Science and Technology in Krakow

10/2011 - 02/2015

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Knowledge in the field of software testing methodology	
Python	
SQL	• • 0 0 0
HTTP Protocol	• 0 0 0 0
Testing REST API	• 0 0 0 0
Experience with Windows and Linux	• 0 0 0 0
Git	• 0 0 0 0
Postman	• 0 0 0 0
Computer Networks	• 0 0 0 0

SOFT SKILLS

Analytical thinking, problem solving and research skills

Communicative, team player

Proactive and self-motivated

CERTIFICATES

ISTQB Certified Tester Foundation Level (05/2020 - Present)

LANGUAGES

English

INTERESTS

Mountain trekking

Pilates

Adventure books, reportages